[{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981442959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":9113,"timeElapsed":22923},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981450410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7447,"timeElapsed":30373},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981454334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3922,"timeElapsed":34298},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981456369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2033,"timeElapsed":36333},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981458365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1994,"timeElapsed":38329},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981460577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2209,"timeElapsed":40541},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981462882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2302,"timeElapsed":42846},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981464819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1934,"timeElapsed":44783},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981467135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2312,"timeElapsed":47099},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981476361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":8119,"timeElapsed":56325},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981478889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2525,"timeElapsed":58853},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981481730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2835,"timeElapsed":61694},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981483502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1768,"timeElapsed":63466},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981485567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2062,"timeElapsed":65531},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981487707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2136,"timeElapsed":67671},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981490284,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2574,"timeElapsed":70247},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981492609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2324,"timeElapsed":72573},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981495149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2538,"timeElapsed":75113},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981502803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6404,"timeElapsed":82767},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981505079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2274,"timeElapsed":85043},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981508045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2964,"timeElapsed":88009},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981511078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3028,"timeElapsed":91041},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981513819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2740,"timeElapsed":93783},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981516057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2236,"timeElapsed":96021},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981517986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1927,"timeElapsed":97950},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981520408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":100372},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981523519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3108,"timeElapsed":103483},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981537760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":13272,"timeElapsed":117724},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981544426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6664,"timeElapsed":124390},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981547401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2972,"timeElapsed":127365},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981550124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2721,"timeElapsed":130088},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981553640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3514,"timeElapsed":133604},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981560801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":7159,"timeElapsed":140765},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981566157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5354,"timeElapsed":146121},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981571854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5695,"timeElapsed":151818},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981574635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2779,"timeElapsed":154599},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981580904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5327,"timeElapsed":160868},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981584169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3263,"timeElapsed":164133},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981586300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2128,"timeElapsed":166264},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981588839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2536,"timeElapsed":168803},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981590766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1925,"timeElapsed":170730},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981594390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3622,"timeElapsed":174354},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981596502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2110,"timeElapsed":176466},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981598537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2034,"timeElapsed":178501},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981600203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1664,"timeElapsed":180167},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981609610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8232,"timeElapsed":189574},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981612188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":192151},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981615472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3280,"timeElapsed":195436},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981617595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2121,"timeElapsed":197559},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981620102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2505,"timeElapsed":200066},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981624268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4164,"timeElapsed":204232},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981626061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1790,"timeElapsed":206025},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981629083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3020,"timeElapsed":209046},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981632125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3040,"timeElapsed":212089},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981636931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3717,"timeElapsed":216895},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981639993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3060,"timeElapsed":219957},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981641949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1953,"timeElapsed":221913},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981644187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2235,"timeElapsed":224150},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981655997,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11808,"timeElapsed":235961},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981658777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2778,"timeElapsed":238741},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981661132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2352,"timeElapsed":241095},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981663718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2583,"timeElapsed":243682},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981666353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2633,"timeElapsed":246317},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981668224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"52","question":"What does family mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1868,"timeElapsed":248188},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981672970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3436,"timeElapsed":252934},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981674936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1964,"timeElapsed":254900},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981677436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2497,"timeElapsed":257400},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981680623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3185,"timeElapsed":260587},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981688441,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7815,"timeElapsed":268405},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981692442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4000,"timeElapsed":272406},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981694922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2478,"timeElapsed":274886},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981697694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2771,"timeElapsed":277658},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981700029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2332,"timeElapsed":279993},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981703487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"93","question":"What keeps you up at night?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3456,"timeElapsed":283451},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981717391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":12079,"timeElapsed":297355},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981719513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":299477},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981722709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3194,"timeElapsed":302673},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981726004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3292,"timeElapsed":305967},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981727736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1730,"timeElapsed":307700},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981730556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2818,"timeElapsed":310520},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981732949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":312912},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981735120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2168,"timeElapsed":315083},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981737298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2177,"timeElapsed":317262},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981782279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":43756,"timeElapsed":362242},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981784611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2330,"timeElapsed":364575},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981792324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7711,"timeElapsed":372288},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981795986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3661,"timeElapsed":375950},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981798389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2400,"timeElapsed":378353},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981800878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":380842},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981805355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4474,"timeElapsed":385319},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981808183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2826,"timeElapsed":388147},{"subjectID":"8ub20asjb2","prolificID":"66140c26ed884c5d523440f5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b224985bdff8deeee356","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981811196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"73","question":"What’s something you believe in that other people close to you do not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3011,"timeElapsed":391160}]